Finding Aid for the Donald A. Glaser Papers, 1943-2013, bulk 1949-2003 GlaserDA
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Series 6 Molecular Biology, 1958-2005; 6
  - Subseries 8 UC Berkeley Virus Lab and departmental material, 1961-1996
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_08 (Box B-6.10, Folder 8)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_09 (Box B-6.10, Folder 9)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_10 (Box B-6.10, Folder 10)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_11 (Box B-6.10, Folder 11)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_12 (Box B-6.10, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_13 (Box B-6.10, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_14 (Box B-6.10, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_15 (Box B-6.10, Folder 15)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_16 (Box B-6.10, Folder 16)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_17 (Box B-6.10, Folder 17)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_18 (Box B-6.10, Folder 18)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_19 (Box B-6.10, Folder 19)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_20 (Box B-6.10, Folder 20)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_21 (Box B-6.10, Folder 21)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_22 (Box B-6.10, Folder 22)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_23 (Box B-6.10, Folder 23)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_24 (Box B-6.10, Folder 24)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_25 (Box B-6.10, Folder 25)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_26 (Box B-6.10, Folder 26)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_27 (Box B-6.10, Folder 27)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_28 (Box B-6.10, Folder 28)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_29 (Box B-6.10, Folder 29)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_30 (Box B-6.10, Folder 30)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_31 (Box B-6.10, Folder 31)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_32 (Box B-6.10, Folder 32)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: assorted photos and slides (many unidentified), ca. 1970-1971; GlaserDA_06_08_10B_32a (Box B-6.10, Folder 32a)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: program, 1970-1972; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_19 (Box B-6.7, Folder 19)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: John Couch's reports, 1971-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_29 (Box B-6.7, Folder 29)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: John Couch's reports, 1971-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_30 (Box B-6.7, Folder 30)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Budgets, 1971-1983; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_11 (Box B-6.7, Folder 11)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Alexander J.C. Para's reports, 1972-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_14 (Box B-6.8, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Ron Baker's reports, 1973-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_23 (Box B-6.7, Folder 23)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: John Bercovitz's reports, 1973-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_24 (Box B-6.7, Folder 24)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Larry Johnson's reports, 1973-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_08 (Box B-6.8, Folder 8)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Larry Johnson's reports, 1973-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_09 (Box B-6.8, Folder 9)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Bob Henry's reports, 1973-1981; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_06 (Box B-6.8, Folder 6)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Bob Henry's reports, 1973-1981; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_07 (Box B-6.8, Folder 7)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Jeff Watts' reports, 1974-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_16 (Box B-6.8, Folder 16)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Mike Konrad's reports, 1974-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_10 (Box B-6.8, Folder 10)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Mike Konrad's reports, 1974-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_11 (Box B-6.8, Folder 11)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Mike Konrad's reports, 1974-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_12 (Box B-6.8, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Mutant Collection, 1974-1982; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_10 (Box B-6.7, Folder 10)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Oliver Hankinson's reports, 1975-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_02 (Box B-6.8, Folder 2)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: David Busch's reports, 1976-1980; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_26 (Box B-6.7, Folder 26)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: David Busch's reports, 1976-1980; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_27 (Box B-6.7, Folder 27)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: David Busch's reports, 1976-1980; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_28 (Box B-6.7, Folder 28)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: budget reports, ca. 1977; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_17 (Box B-6.7, Folder 17)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Jim Berk's reports, 1977; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_25 (Box B-6.7, Folder 25)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Annual Report, 1977-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_09 (Box B-6.7, Folder 9)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Space, 1977-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_05 (Box B-6.7, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: work schedules, 1977-1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_07 (Box B-6.7, Folder 7)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Paul M. Abersold reports, 1977-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_21 (Box B-6.7, Folder 21)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Dan Quincy's reports, 1977-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_15 (Box B-6.8, Folder 15)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Operations, 1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_06 (Box B-6.7, Folder 6)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: site visit, 1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_08 (Box B-6.7, Folder 8)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Microprocessor, controls, 1978; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_13 (Box B-6.7, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Karl Mellander's reports, 1978-1979; GlaserDA_06_08_08B_13 (Box B-6.8, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Virus Lab: Bruce Aidells' reports, 1979; GlaserDA_06_08_07B_22 (Box B-6.7, Folder 22)
    - Molecular Biology: faculty memos, 1986-1992; GlaserDA_06_08_13B_17 (Box B-6.13, Folder 17)
    - Molecular Biology: graduate affairs, 1986-1996; GlaserDA_06_08_15B_12 (Box B-6.15, Folder 12)
    - Annual reports, Virus Lab, 1989-1991; GlaserDA_06_08_14B_13 (Box B-6.14, Folder 13)
    - Molecular Biology: department memos, 1991-1996; GlaserDA_06_08_15B_07 (Box B-6.15, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate research assistant administrative, 1992-1993; GlaserDA_06_08_16B_10 (Box B-6.16, Folder 10)
    - Undergraduate research assistant administrative, 1992-1993; GlaserDA_06_08_16B_11 (Box B-6.16, Folder 11)
    - Molecular Biology: Research Task Assistant Program, 1993-1996; GlaserDA_06_08_15B_11 (Box B-6.15, Folder 11)
    - Molecular Biology: course, 1995-1996; GlaserDA_06_08_15B_09 (Box B-6.15, Folder 9)
- Series 7 Neuroscience, 1981-2008; 7
  - Subseries 1 Notes, 1981-2006
    - Neuroscience I, 1981-1982; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_01 (Box C-7.1, Folder 1)
    - Color, 1981; 1984; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_02 (Box C-7.1, Folder 2)
    - Retinex theory, ca. 1982; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_03 (Box C-7.1, Folder 3)
    - Neuroscience II, 1983; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_04 (Box C-7.1, Folder 4)
    - Notebook I, 1984 June - July; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_05 (Box C-7.1, Folder 5)
    - Spatial vision, ca. 1984; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_06 (Box C-7.1, Folder 6)
    - Cellular automata, ca. 1984-1985; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_07 (Box C-7.1, Folder 7)
    - Notebook II, 1985 January - March; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_08 (Box C-7.1, Folder 8)
    - Notebook III, 1985 March - May; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_09 (Box C-7.1, Folder 9)
    - Neuroscience III, 1985-1986; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_10 (Box C-7.1, Folder 10)
    - System analysis - Vision, 1985 - 1987; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_11 (Box C-7.1, Folder 11)
    - Texture and textons, 1985 April; 1987 March; GlaserDA_07_01_01C_12 (Box C-7.1, Folder 12)
    - Reductionism, 1985 July - August; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_01 (Box C-7.2, Folder 1)
    - Cortical theory, 1985 November; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_02 (Box C-7.2, Folder 2)
    - Motion Theory, 1986-1987; 1990; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_03 (Box C-7.2, Folder 3)
    - Notebook IV, 1986 June; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_04 (Box C-7.2, Folder 4)
    - Correlation theory, 1986 July - 1987 March; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_05 (Box C-7.2, Folder 5)
    - Notebook V, 1986 August; 1988 March; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_06 (Box C-7.2, Folder 6)
    - Neuroscience IV, 1986 August - 1988 September; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_07 (Box C-7.2, Folder 7)
    - Depth theory, 1986 October - 1987 January; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_08 (Box C-7.2, Folder 8)
    - Shift theory, 1986 November - 1987 April; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_09 (Box C-7.2, Folder 9)
    - Structure, 1986 December - 1987 February; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_10 (Box C-7.2, Folder 10)
    - Network theory, 1987 January - September; GlaserDA_07_01_02C_11 (Box C-7.2, Folder 11)
    - Apparent motion, 1987 December - 1988 January; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_01 (Box C-7.3, Folder 1)
    - Neuroscience V, 1989 October - 1990 September; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_02 (Box C-7.3, Folder 2)
    - Neuroscience VI, 1991-1992; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_03 (Box C-7.3, Folder 3)
    - Neuroscience VII, 1994-1997; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_04 (Box C-7.3, Folder 4)
    - Image-side perspective (NSA lecture notes), 1997; GlaserDA_07_01_14B_33a (Box B-7.14, Folder 33a)
    - Notebook VI, 1999 April; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_05 (Box C-7.3, Folder 5)
    - Neuroscience VIII, 1999 May - 2000 December; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_06 (Box C-7.3, Folder 6)
    - Neuroscience IX, 2001 March - December; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_07 (Box C-7.3, Folder 7)
    - Stereo, pp. 1-120, 2002 January - April; GlaserDA_07_01_03C_08 (Box C-7.3, Folder 8)
    - Neuroscience X, 2002; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_01 (Box C-7.4, Folder 1)
    - Data graphs and transparencies, ca. 2002; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_02 (Box C-7.4, Folder 2)
    - Neuroscience XI, 2003; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_03 (Box C-7.4, Folder 3)
    - Neuroscience XII, 2004; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_04 (Box C-7.4, Folder 4)
    - Neuroscience XIII, 2005 January - 2006 July; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_05 (Box C-7.4, Folder 5)
    - Neuroscience XIV, undated; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_06 (Box C-7.4, Folder 6)
    - Transparencies, undated; GlaserDA_07_01_04C_07 (Box C-7.4, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2 Writings and talks, 1983-2006
    - Articles featured in Italian newspaper, Il Tempo, 1983 October - 1984 January; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_01 (Box C-7.5, Folder 1)
      Photocopies, translations
    - A physicist's view of vision, Bioscience at the Physical Science Frontier: Proceedings of a Foundation Symposium on the 150th Anniversary of Alfred Nobel's Birth, 1983-1985; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_02 (Box C-7.5, Folder 2)
      Notes, correspondence, transcripts
    - A physicist's view of vision (manuscript, proof, correspondence), 1987; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_29 (Box B-7.15, Folder 29)
    - Is there life after reductionism?, 1985 August; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_03 (Box C-7.5, Folder 3)
      Lecture notes, flyer
    - The musician as conjurer, San Francisco Symphony Lecture Series, 1986; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_04 (Box C-7.5, Folder 4)
      Notes, related material
    - Motion interference in speed discrimination (reprint), 1989; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_13 (Box B-7.15, Folder 13)
    - Psychophysical evidence for a bilateral projection from retina to cortex in humans (manuscript, correspondence, notes), 1989; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_28 (Box B-7.15, Folder 28)
    - Long range effects on discrimination of local depth, 1990 April - 1991 January; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_05 (Box C-7.5, Folder 5)
      Drafts, reviews
    - Research Note: Some further observations on visual inertia, 1990-1992; GlaserDA_07_02_16B_01 (Box B-7.16, Folder 1)
    - Influence of remote objects on local depth perception (manuscript, reprint, correspondence), 1991; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_34 (Box B-7.14, Folder 34)
    - Influence of remote objects on local depth perception, Vision Research Vol. 32, No. 10 1991, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_06 (Box C-7.5, Folder 6)
      Photocopy
    - Metastable motion anisotropy (reprint and correspondence), 1991; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_06 (Box B-7.15, Folder 6)
    - Human discrimination of images of different fractal statistic (manuscript), 1992; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_31 (Box B-7.14, Folder 31)
    - Shape analysis and stereopsis for human depth perception (reprints), 1991; GlaserDA_07_02_16B_03 (Box B-7.16, Folder 3)
    - Shape analysis and stereopsis for human depth perception, Vision Research Vol. 32, No. 3 1992 March, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_07 (Box C-7.5, Folder 7)
      Photocopy, draft
    - Depth discrimination of a line is improved by adding other nearby lines (manuscript, reprint, correspondence), 1991-1992; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_21 (Box B-7.14, Folder 21)
    - Depth discrimination of a line is improved by adding other nearby lines, Vision Research Vol. 32, No. 9 1992 September, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_08 (Box C-7.5, Folder 8)
    - Temporal aspects of depth contrast (manuscript and correspondence), 1992; GlaserDA_07_02_16B_08 (Box B-7.16, Folder 8)
    - Temporal aspects of depth contrast, Vision Research Vol. 33, No. 7 1993 May, 1992 September - 1993 May; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_09 (Box C-7.5, Folder 9)
      Drafts
    - Comparison of human performance with algorithms for estimating fractal dimension of fractional Brownian statistics, Journal of the Optical Society of America A Vol. 10, No. 6 1993 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_10 (Box C-7.5, Folder 10)
    - Perceived motion of a colored spot in a noisy achromatic background, Perception Vol. 22, No. 10 1993 October, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_11 (Box C-7.5, Folder 11)
      Reprint, draft
    - Perceived motion of a colored spot in a noisy achromatic background (manuscript, proof, correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_20 (Box B-7.15, Folder 20)
    - Perceived motion of a colored spot in a noisy achromatic background (manuscript, proof, correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_21 (Box B-7.15, Folder 21)
    - Perception of motion in a noisy environment (manuscript and correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_22 (Box B-7.15, Folder 22)
    - Initial performance, learning and observer variability for hyperacuity tasks (manuscript, reprint, correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_35 (Box B-7.14, Folder 35)
    - Initial performance, learning and observer variability for hyperacuity tasks, Vision Research Vol. 33, No. 16 1993 November, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_12 (Box C-7.5, Folder 12)
    - Comparison of human performance with algorithms for estimating fractal dimension of fractional Brownian statistics (manuscript, reprints, correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_17 (Box B-7.14, Folder 17)
    - Exploring brain functions: epilogue reprints, 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_27 (Box B-7.14, Folder 27)
    - Human motion perception of small moving targets in noisy environments (manuscript and correspondence), 1993; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_32 (Box B-7.14, Folder 32)
    - Some temporal aspects of stereoactivity (manuscript, reprints, correspondence), 1993-1994; GlaserDA_07_02_16B_04 (Box B-7.16, Folder 4)
    - Some temporal aspects of stereoacuity, Vision Research Vol. 34, No. 7 1994 April, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_13 (Box C-7.5, Folder 13)
    - Depth discrimination of a crowded line is better when it is more luminant than the lines crowding it (manuscript and correspondence), 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_22 (Box B-7.14, Folder 22)
    - Multi-channel models of early vision, 1995; GlaserDA_07_02_15B_14 (Box B-7.15, Folder 14)
    - Depth discrimination of a crowded line is better when it is more luminant than the lines crowding it, Vision Research Vol. 35, No. 5 1995 March, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_14 (Box C-7.5, Folder 14)
    - Depth of uniocular features in simple stereograms (manuscript and correspondence), 1995-1996; GlaserDA_07_02_14B_23 (Box B-7.14, Folder 23)
    - Motion detection and characterization by an excitable membrane: The "bow wave" model, Neurocomputing Vols. 26-27, 1999 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_15 (Box C-7.5, Folder 15)
    - Slowly moving stimuli induce characteristic periodic activity waves in an excitable membrane model of visual motion processing, Neurocomputing Vols. 44-46, 2002 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_16 (Box C-7.5, Folder 16)
    - Synaptic depression and facilitation can induce motion aftereffects in an excitable membrane model of visual motion processing, Neurocomputing Vols. 44-46, 2002 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_17 (Box C-7.5, Folder 17)
    - Edges and line minimally mask width discrimination of rectangles, Neurocomputing Vols. 44-46, 2002 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_18 (Box C-7.5, Folder 18)
      Reprint
    - Interaction among cortical maps, Neurocomputing Vols. 44-46, 2002 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_19 (Box C-7.5, Folder 19)
    - Political science, California Monthly, 2004 September; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_20 (Box C-7.5, Folder 20)
      Email copy
    - The influence of cortical feature maps on the encoding of the orientation of a short line, Journal of Computational Neuroscience Vol. 20, No. 3 2006 June, GlaserDA_07_02_05C_21 (Box C-7.5, Folder 21)
    - Talk on color vision (untitled), undated; GlaserDA_07_02_05C_22 (Box C-7.5, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 3 Technical, administrative, and other papers, 1981-2003
    - Writings by others, 1981; 2002; 2003; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_01 (Box C-7.6, Folder 1)
    - Neurosciences Research Program, 1981-1982; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_20 (Box B-7.13, Folder 20)
    - Neuroscience, miscellaneous, 1981-1982; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_21 (Box B-7.13, Folder 21)
    - Optometry, 1981-1983; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_26 (Box B-7.13, Folder 26)
    - Research Program (description), 1981-1983; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_31 (Box B-7.13, Folder 31)
    - Seminars/lectures, 1981-1983; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_33 (Box B-7.13, Folder 33)
    - Grant proposal: System Development Foundation, 1982; GlaserDA_07_03_12B_25 (Box B-7.12, Folder 25)
    - New York, 1982; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_22 (Box B-7.13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1987; 2001; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_02 (Box C-7.6, Folder 2)
    - Grant proposals 1982-1985, GlaserDA_07_03_06C_03 (Box C-7.6, Folder 3)
    - Article clippings, 1983; 2003; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_04 (Box C-7.6, Folder 4)
    - Jitendra Malik, 1986; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_09 (Box B-7.13, Folder 9)
    - Sam Bowne reports, 1986 May - 1987 March; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_05 (Box C-7.6, Folder 5)
    - Tribhawan Kumar projects and reports, 1986-1989; 2001; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_06 (Box C-7.6, Folder 6)
    - Interdisciplinary Conference, New York, 1986-1991; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_36 (Box B-7.14, Folder 36)
    - Neurobiology Division: information and memos, 1987-1990; GlaserDA_07_03_13B_19 (Box B-7.13, Folder 19)
    - National Science Foundation, 1988-1991; GlaserDA_07_03_15B_17 (Box B-7.15, Folder 17)
    - Biomedical Research Support Grant, 1989-1991; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_14 (Box B-7.14, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Research Grant application, 1990-1994; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_29 (Box B-7.14, Folder 29)
    - Grant proposals 1990-1996, GlaserDA_07_03_06C_07 (Box C-7.6, Folder 7)
    - Neurobiology faculty, 1991-1993; GlaserDA_07_03_15B_19 (Box B-7.15, Folder 19)
    - Sponsor's Projects Office, 1991-1993; GlaserDA_07_03_16B_05 (Box B-7.16, Folder 5)
    - Vision Science, 1992; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_03 (Box B-7.14, Folder 3)
    - Book proposals, 1992; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_15 (Box B-7.14, Folder 15)
    - Kumar reviews, 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_37 (Box B-7.14, Folder 37)
    - Kumar reviews, 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_38 (Box B-7.14, Folder 38)
    - Kumar reviews, 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_39 (Box B-7.14, Folder 39)
    - Reviews, 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_16B_02 (Box B-7.16, Folder 2)
    - Stereopsis due to luminance difference in the two eyes (manuscript and corrspondence), 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_16B_06 (Box B-7.16, Folder 6)
    - Stereopsis due to luminance difference in the two eyes (manuscript and corrspondence), 1993-1995; GlaserDA_07_03_16B_07 (Box B-7.16, Folder 7)
    - Multiple matching of features in simple stereograms (manuscript, proof, correspondence), 1995; GlaserDA_07_03_15B_15 (Box B-7.15, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 2000-2002; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_08 (Box C-7.6, Folder 8)
    - Grant proposals 2001-2003, GlaserDA_07_03_06C_09 (Box C-7.6, Folder 9)
    - Racetrack experiment material, undated; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_10 (Box C-7.6, Folder 10)
    - Color filter sheets, undated; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_11 (Box C-7.6, Folder 11)
    - Optical images, undated; GlaserDA_07_03_06C_12 (Box C-7.6, Folder 12)
    - A geometrical ambiguity in depth perception (manuscript), undated; GlaserDA_07_03_14B_33 (Box B-7.14, Folder 33)
    - Tomaso A. Poggio (bio-bibliography), undated; GlaserDA_07_03_15B_30 (Box B-7.15, Folder 30)
    - Tomaso A. Poggio (bio-bibliography), undated; GlaserDA_07_03_15B_31 (Box B-7.15, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 4 Born-digital material, 2001-2008
    The majority of this subseries consists of animated images used for visual experiments.
    - World Innovation Foundation material, 2001-2002; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_01 (Box C-7.7, Folder 1)
    - Zebra illusions, 2004 August; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_02 (Box C-7.7, Folder 2)
    - Racetrack movies, 2004-2005; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_03 (Box C-7.7, Folder 3)
    - Lecture and presentation slides, 2004-2005; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_04 (Box C-7.7, Folder 4)
    - Drafts and notes, 2004-2008; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_05 (Box C-7.7, Folder 5)
    - Bow waves and histograms, 2005 January; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_06 (Box C-7.7, Folder 6)
    - Rotating dot patterns, 2005 February; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_07 (Box C-7.7, Folder 7)
    - Stochastic resonance images, 2005 September; GlaserDA_07_04_07C_08 (Box C-7.7, Folder 8)
- Series 8 Audio Visual, ca. 1949-2006; 8
  - Subseries 1 Photographic glass slides, ca. 1949-1981
    - Cloud chamber, ca. 1949; GlaserDA_08_01_01C_01; Lantern slides (Box C-8.1, Folder 1)
      Images appear in dissertation
    - Bubble chamber I, ca. 1951-1960; GlaserDA_08_01_01C_02; Lantern slides (Box C-8.1, Folder 2)
    - Bubble chamber II, ca. 1951-1960; GlaserDA_08_01_02C_01; Lantern slides (Box C-8.2, Folder 1)
    - Bubble chamber III, ca. 1951-1960; GlaserDA_08_01_03C_01; Lantern slides (Box C-8.3, Folder 1)
    - Molecular biology, ca. 1963-1981; GlaserDA_08_01_03C_02; Lantern slides (Box C-8.3, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2 35mm slides, ca. 1951-1988
    - Bubble chamber, ca. 1951-1960; GlaserDA_08_02_04C_01; 35mm (Box C-8.4, Folder 1)
    - Molecular biology and CERN particle data tables, ca.1963-1981; GlaserDA_08_02_04C_02; 35mm (Box C-8.4, Folder 2)
    - Molecular biology, ca. 1963-1981; GlaserDA_08_02_04C_03; 35mm (Box C-8.4, Folder 3)
    - Kolers, P.A. - Figures, ca. 1971; GlaserDA_08_02_04C_04; 35mm (Box C-8.4, Folder 4)
    - Julesz, B. - Texton figures, ca. 1975-1983; GlaserDA_08_02_04C_05; 35mm (Box C-8.4, Folder 5)